&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：好的，让我们谈谈这个关于吊装的练习。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, let's talk about this exercise on hoisting.
这里有一个内联函数表达式。
We have a inline function expression here.
我在讲座中说过，我通常使用单线性函数
And I said in the lecture that I typically do use one-liner functions
作为内联函数表达式。
as inline function expressions.
但为了这个练习的目的，
But just for the purposes of this exercise,
让我们看看当我们将它作为函数内表达式移出时会是什么样子。
let's see what it looks like when we move it out as an in-function expression.
然后你可以自己打电话
And you can then make calls on your own as to whether or
这不是提高或妨碍可读性，好吗？
not that improves or hampers the readability, okay?
所以我可以把它拔出来
So I can pull that out,
我必须将其留在此范围内，因为它确实引用了StudentId。
I have to leave it inside of this scope because it does reference the studentId.
我不能把它作为一个独立的帮手拉出来，
I can't pull it out as some standalone helper,
它在使用StudentId时被关闭。
it is closed over in using the studentId.
但有一件事我很喜欢这种把东西作为函数拉出来的风格
But one thing that I do like about this style of pulling things out as function
声明。
declarations.
使用这些函数的地方最终会读取更多的内容
Is that the places where these functions are used end up reading a lot more
干净利落，没有被函数执行，定义代码中断。
cleanly without being interrupted with function execution, definition code.
所以这个读起来非常干净，
So this reads very cleanly as find,
通过匹配ID，按ID查找学生记录。
by matching the ID, find a student record by ID.
所以把东西拉出来代码风格，
So that style of code of pulling things out,
从可读性的角度来看，即使是一行程序也有一些优点。
even one-liners, does have some advantages from a readability perspective.
好的，让我们在下面做一件类似的事情。
Okay, let's do a similar thing down here.
我们已经使用了一个命名函数，那么这个函数呢？
We already have a named function being used, so what about this function?
我们知道这个函数没有在内部使用任何东西，所以
Well, we know that that function's not using anything internally, so
我们可以把它拉出来作为它自己的独立功能。
we could pull it out as its own standalone function.
所以我会这样做，我们将简单地按名称引用它。
So I will do that, and we will simply reference it by name.
这同样具有可读性的好处，
Which again, has that readability benefit,
现在这类人在做什么就更清楚了。
now it's much clearer what the sort is doing.
与printRecord相同，printRecord本质上是一个独立的
Same thing with printRecord, printRecord is essentially a standalone
函数，可以由引用它本身的名称替换。
function which can be replaced by a name that references it itself.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在，显然意见不一，但是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now, obviously opinions vary, but
我的观点是，这样做会产生更多可读性更强的代码。
my opinion is that produces a lot more readable code to do that.
向下到paidStudentsToEnroll，同样，我们有一个内联筛选函数。
Down to paidStudentsToEnroll, again, we have an inline filter function.
这是内联筛选器函数不是
This is inline filter function is not
使用任何内部变量。
using any of the internal variables.
等等，那个叫什么来着，Need to Enroll，同样的东西，
So wait, what was that called, needToEnroll, same thing,
可以搬出去。
it could be moved out.
正如我在练习的导言中所说的，我们可以选择的原因是，
And as I said in the intro to the exercise, the reason why we can prefer,
从功能提升的角度。
from the perspective of function hoisting.
我们之所以更喜欢把它移到外部范围是因为它更容易，
The reason why we can prefer moving it to the outer scope is that it is easier,
通常，当作用域比较平坦时分析作用域。
generally, to analyze scopes when they are flatter.
作用域嵌套得越深，
The more deeply nested scopes get,
在我们意想不到的地方会发生更多令人困惑的闭包。
the more confusing the closures can happen in places that we're not expecting.
所以我们试着把它们移到范围之外去尝试
So we're trying to move them out to as outer of a scope as we can to try
有一个更简单的范围模型来考虑。
to have a simpler scope model to think about.
好的，getStudentId也是类似的东西，
Okay, getStudentId is a similar thing,
它不是指内部的任何东西，所以
it is not referring to anything internally, so
也就是说，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们可以搬出去。
that is, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: One that we can move out.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：最后，提醒未支付，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then, finally, the remindUnpaid,
我们有这个过滤功能。
we have this filtering function.
也就是不使用内部的任何东西，
Which is, again, not using anything internal,
所以我们可以把它拉到这个外部作用域，并按名称使用它。
so we can pull it out to this outer scope and use it by name.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：最后，我们可以看到所有这些函数都在顶部。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Lastly, we can see that all these functions are at the top.
但由于功能提升，它们并不一定要处于顶端。
But they don't necessarily need to be at the top because of function hoisting.
所以我们要做的就是复制所有这些，
So what we're going to do is copy all of those,
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：然后下来
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And come down here and
把它们放在底部。
put them at the bottom.
然后为了一般的可读性，我喜欢画ASCII线。
And then just for general readability, I like to draw ASCII lines.
线下面的一切都是实现细节，
And everything below the line is implementation detail,
行上面的所有内容都是我的可执行代码。
everything above the line is my executable code.
因此，当我打开文件时，我看到所有要运行的内容都在顶部。
So when I open the file, I see everything right there at the top that's gonna run.
正如我在讲座中提到的，我认为这本质上是理解
As I mentioned in the lecture, I see this as essentially understanding
关于我的工具的一些更详细的信息。
something more detailed about my tool.
并且以我认为会产生积极变化的方式使用我的工具，在这种情况下，
And using my tool in a way that I think effects a positive change, in this case,
为了可读性。
for readability.
因此，当然有一些方法可以使用提升并使代码更加混乱。
So there are certainly ways that you can use hoisting and make code more confusing.
但这并不意味着吊装的所有用法都是坏的。
But that doesn't mean that all usages of hoisting are bad.
我认为有很多方法可以使用提升和使用函数声明和
I think there are ways to use hoisting and use function declarations and
使用嵌套函数或拉出的函数。
use nested functions or functions that are pulled out.
我认为有一些方法可以让您的代码更具可读性。
I think there are ways to do that in which you can make your code more readable.
嗯，希望这就是你从这个练习中得到的收获。
Well, hopefully that's the takeaway you get from this exercise.
对您来说，这是一个值得分析代码的冒险。
Is that that's a worthwhile venture for you to analyze about your code.